<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-08-30T21:03:38-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Life of One T.England</title><subtitle>In the every changing rollercoaster of life this blog is to highlight some  of the day to day things that I go through. It will highlight the parts of my life that are great challenges I faced, awesome adventures that I got to  experience, the small and little joys that come at random moments, and even  the frustarions I have. This will be a place that any thing on my mind will  have a safe space to live and be shared amongst any who stumble upon it too.
</subtitle><author><name>Taryn England</name></author><entry><title type="html">Introduction Post</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/misc/2023/08/30/Introduction-Post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Introduction Post" /><published>2023-08-30T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-08-30T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/misc/2023/08/30/Introduction-Post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/misc/2023/08/30/Introduction-Post.html"><![CDATA[<p>In this first post I will unfold the journey in which I took to even get to post here.</p>

<p>The setup trying to get this first post was very rough at first. I struggled a lot with getting the needed software downloaded where it needed to get downloaded and really felt defeated. After a couple hours of trying and not getting anywhere I had to step away and work on other things that were needing to get down and I knew I could do. After wrapping the other work I decided to get some food and hoped that with some food in my system I might be able to come back to trying things working and it would be less defeating. To my surprise I was right!</p>

<p>I have written a blog post before so the idea of blogging isn’t new to me but I have never written a blog post in this manner of coding it. I have used blog websites before and I just had to write into the text field and the website took care of everything after I hit post.</p>

<p>I feel like over the course of the next few months I will learn and understand more on the nature of what is actually going on between what I see on my local computer and how that gets posted on the internet for anyone to be able to see around the world. It still is a little foggy on what is actually happening behind the scenes.</p>

<p>A few links that proved <strong>very helpful</strong> during my journey:</p>

<ol>
  <li>
    <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3fWovzfcsfk">The Last of the Mohicans Calming Music &amp; Ambience for Relaxation, Sleep, and Studying By: Ambient Worlds</a></p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZZ5LpwO-An4">HEYYEYAAEYAAAEYAEYAA By: ProtoOfSnagem</a></p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JImcvtJzIK8">Why is the Rum Gone? -Remix By: DaJugglingFool</a></p>
  </li>
</ol>]]></content><author><name>Taryn England</name></author><category term="misc" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this first post I will unfold the journey in which I took to even get to post here.]]></summary></entry></feed>